[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "I'm sure you don't mind being called a star then Lupita?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "being", "called", "a", "star", "then", "Lupita", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "But no, a star is born.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "no", ",", "a", "star", "is", "born", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lupita"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey", "Alabama"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Tell me what's going on?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "It is snowing from New Jersey to Alabama, and just on the eastern side of the snow it's freezing rain and sleet.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "snowing", "from", "New", "Jersey", "to", "Alabama", ",", "and", "just", "on", "the", "eastern", "side", "of", "the", "snow", "it", "'s", "freezing", "rain", "and", "sleet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What's going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Piers, what a difference two week makes.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "what", "a", "difference", "two", "week", "makes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kenya"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Where have you been?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "have", "you", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Wow, I've been in Kenya, you know, basking in the sun and getting ready for this.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "in", "Kenya", ",", "you", "know", ",", "basking", "in", "the", "sun", "and", "getting", "ready", "for", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Getting ready, preparing for the onslaught?", "question_tokens": ["Getting", "ready", ",", "preparing", "for", "the", "onslaught", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "I'm sure you don't mind being called the star then Lupita?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "being", "called", "the", "star", "then", "Lupita", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "But no, a star is born.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "no", ",", "a", "star", "is", "born", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lupita"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Was it like a real moment?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "like", "a", "real", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "CQUEEN: Beyond.", "answer_tokens": ["CQUEEN", ":", "Beyond", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "or you didn't have a clue?", "question_tokens": ["or", "you", "did", "n't", "have", "a", "clue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Patsey", "Patsey"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Did you gave your everything?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "gave", "your", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yeah, and, you know, Patsey -- whenever Patsey speaks it's from a place of extremist.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Patsey", "--", "whenever", "Patsey", "speaks", "it", "'s", "from", "a", "place", "of", "extremist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Haven"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "So, where, where you when you got the call from this man that was going to change your life?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "where", ",", "where", "you", "when", "you", "got", "the", "call", "from", "this", "man", "that", "was", "going", "to", "change", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I was on my way out of my apartment in New Haven.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "on", "my", "way", "out", "of", "my", "apartment", "in", "New", "Haven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Were you emotional?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "emotional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Did you cry?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "cry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "This girl's amazing, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "girl", "'s", "amazing", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And when the horse went Lupita Nyong'o, what were you doing in that moment?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "the", "horse", "went", "Lupita", "Nyong'o", ",", "what", "were", "you", "doing", "in", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I raised my hand up and I just closed my eyes and cried and said thank you, thank you, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "raised", "my", "hand", "up", "and", "I", "just", "closed", "my", "eyes", "and", "cried", "and", "said", "thank", "you", ",", "thank", "you", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lupita Nyong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad Pitt"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, you know, well Brad Pitt is one of those names that everyone's heard but I guess he just could place it (ph), you know, what was important was whether he knew him personally or not.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "well", "Brad", "Pitt", "is", "one", "of", "those", "names", "that", "everyone", "'s", "heard", "but", "I", "guess", "he", "just", "could", "place", "it", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "was", "important", "was", "whether", "he", "knew", "him", "personally", "or", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Did you think it would have quite the impact of resonance that it's had?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "it", "would", "have", "quite", "the", "impact", "of", "resonance", "that", "it", "'s", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "No, but I'm just so grateful that it has.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "just", "so", "grateful", "that", "it", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "It's wonderful while it goes, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "wonderful", "while", "it", "goes", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "I'll talk to the man who's seen it all before, Arsenio Hall is live and in the house, great man how are you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "talk", "to", "the", "man", "who", "'s", "seen", "it", "all", "before", ",", "Arsenio", "Hall", "is", "live", "and", "in", "the", "house", ",", "great", "man", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Good to see you, buddy.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "to", "see", "you", ",", "buddy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arsenio Hall"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "That he's going?", "question_tokens": ["That", "he", "'s", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "It doesn't feel right but that's because he's my friend.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "feel", "right", "but", "that", "'s", "because", "he", "'s", "my", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Is it just because he was number one for so long?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "just", "because", "he", "was", "number", "one", "for", "so", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Yeah, I mean he's ...", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "mean", "he", "'s", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Carson"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Who's being the best?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "being", "the", "best", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, Johnny Carson is the best.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Johnny", "Carson", "is", "the", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Allen"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Can anyone ever beat the Carson grip on the American audience or simply because he was the only one really for a long period doing it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "anyone", "ever", "beat", "the", "Carson", "grip", "on", "the", "American", "audience", "or", "simply", "because", "he", "was", "the", "only", "one", "really", "for", "a", "long", "period", "doing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "You know, he kind of taught my generation how to do it and as I said that, I started thinking Steve Allen was brilliant.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "he", "kind", "of", "taught", "my", "generation", "how", "to", "do", "it", "and", "as", "I", "said", "that", ",", "I", "started", "thinking", "Steve", "Allen", "was", "brilliant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "If you're going to put money on which Jimmy to win the new war who would be the winner?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "put", "money", "on", "which", "Jimmy", "to", "win", "the", "new", "war", "who", "would", "be", "the", "winner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jimmy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do you say it on air on your show?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "say", "it", "on", "air", "on", "your", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I call you that when we're off the air.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "call", "you", "that", "when", "we", "'re", "off", "the", "air", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Should it just be decommissioned as a word if you take the assumption which is the correct one that is inherently offensive?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "it", "just", "be", "decommissioned", "as", "a", "word", "if", "you", "take", "the", "assumption", "which", "is", "the", "correct", "one", "that", "is", "inherently", "offensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "As a comedian...", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "comedian", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 382, "question": "... was fantastic, right?", "question_tokens": ["...", "was", "fantastic", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "ALL: Well, it's just...", "answer_tokens": ["ALL", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "... and he was welcoming the father, right?", "question_tokens": ["...", "and", "he", "was", "welcoming", "the", "father", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Well, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "I don't know how you would feel, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "you", "would", "feel", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GN"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "How do they know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "they", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "By the way, there's a GN who anonymously said this guy won't get dropped.", "answer_tokens": ["By", "the", "way", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "GN", "who", "anonymously", "said", "this", "guy", "wo", "n't", "get", "dropped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason Brown", "Jason Brown"], "LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Does he know you had a connection to one of Olympics -- America's Olympics athletes?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "know", "you", "had", "a", "connection", "to", "one", "of", "Olympics", "--", "America", "'s", "Olympics", "athletes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "IN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Jason Brown -- Chicago's Jason Brown.", "answer_tokens": ["Jason", "Brown", "--", "Chicago", "'s", "Jason", "Brown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "You extended (ph) and then you have to go wait?", "question_tokens": ["You", "extended", "(", "ph", ")", "and", "then", "you", "have", "to", "go", "wait", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Yeah, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "A text?", "question_tokens": ["A", "text", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "So you're sitting with your phone?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "sitting", "with", "your", "phone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Do you sit there as a sports fan really enjoying it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "sit", "there", "as", "a", "sports", "fan", "really", "enjoying", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "IN", ",", "``", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Why can't they all just come out together?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "they", "all", "just", "come", "out", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "This is when you know you're not enjoying it when you start looking for the countries like with two guys and you laugh, \"What he got was a bow and arrow.\"", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "when", "you", "know", "you", "'re", "not", "enjoying", "it", "when", "you", "start", "looking", "for", "the", "countries", "like", "with", "two", "guys", "and", "you", "laugh", ",", "``", "What", "he", "got", "was", "a", "bow", "and", "arrow", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "You've been mocking people, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "mocking", "people", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Want to go skating later?", "question_tokens": ["Want", "to", "go", "skating", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Let's talk about Black history month.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "talk", "about", "Black", "history", "month", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Well, didn't Morgan Freeman make a statement about this?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "did", "n't", "Morgan", "Freeman", "make", "a", "statement", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Morgan Freeman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Is he right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "... but has it drawn out more racism having the first black American president for example?", "question_tokens": ["...", "but", "has", "it", "drawn", "out", "more", "racism", "having", "the", "first", "black", "American", "president", "for", "example", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "That's possible.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "When you walk around in America now, do you yourself experience any over racism because people know who you are?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "walk", "around", "in", "America", "now", ",", "do", "you", "yourself", "experience", "any", "over", "racism", "because", "people", "know", "who", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I, you know, I don't experience racism.", "answer_tokens": ["I", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "experience", "racism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Did you follow what happened to Samuel L. Jackson?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "follow", "what", "happened", "to", "Samuel", "L.", "Jackson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Samuel L. Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "And that's why you said it right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "why", "you", "said", "it", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Well, now, what was your wish?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "now", ",", "what", "was", "your", "wish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Late night, baby.", "answer_tokens": ["Late", "night", ",", "baby", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "What are you proudest of all your accomplishments?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "proudest", "of", "all", "your", "accomplishments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Mexico has never won a Winter Olympic gold medal, are you confident?", "question_tokens": ["Mexico", "has", "never", "won", "a", "Winter", "Olympic", "gold", "medal", ",", "are", "you", "confident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "No, I'm not confident to win a Winter Olympic gold medal, I'm confident to maybe, you know, make my country proud of me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "confident", "to", "win", "a", "Winter", "Olympic", "gold", "medal", ",", "I", "'m", "confident", "to", "maybe", ",", "you", "know", ",", "make", "my", "country", "proud", "of", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mexico"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Have you pick some of this everyone talking about his eyes?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "pick", "some", "of", "this", "everyone", "talking", "about", "his", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "There really is no (ph) into your talent, is there Prince Hubertus?", "question_tokens": ["There", "really", "is", "no", "(", "ph", ")", "into", "your", "talent", ",", "is", "there", "Prince", "Hubertus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "No, I mean, it's a strange story but it kind of develops like that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "strange", "story", "but", "it", "kind", "of", "develops", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hubertus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Oh, you do?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "I do, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "JJ", "IN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 680, "question": "What impact do that have on you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "impact", "do", "that", "have", "on", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Courage, integrity, you know, anybody who was abandoned, I mean, to you as a father is the best domain crutch (ph) in a man's life and stay for a reason because you know if that ever comes down to it, you got your own father who lean up against...", "answer_tokens": ["Courage", ",", "integrity", ",", "you", "know", ",", "anybody", "who", "was", "abandoned", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "to", "you", "as", "a", "father", "is", "the", "best", "domain", "crutch", "(", "ph", ")", "in", "a", "man", "'s", "life", "and", "stay", "for", "a", "reason", "because", "you", "know", "if", "that", "ever", "comes", "down", "to", "it", ",", "you", "got", "your", "own", "father", "who", "lean", "up", "against", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "So what did you thought what your father made of you being Oscar nominee?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "did", "you", "thought", "what", "your", "father", "made", "of", "you", "being", "Oscar", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Oh, he loved it.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "he", "loved", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]